http://www.kwsonline.com/privacy-policy/

Starting at $6.47/month
Hosting at its best since 1996!
Purchase Now!
Get Online
Content Management System (CMS)
Privacy PolicyHome / Privacy Policy
[printfriendly]
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Knight Web Services® Inc. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of this Website (each, a “User”).
Privacy Users’ privacy is very important to Knight Web Services® Inc. Knight Web Services® Inc. is committed to safeguarding the information Users entrust to Knight Web Services® Inc.
The Information We Collect Knight Web Services® Inc. may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information. Knight Web Services® Inc. may also collect information about how Users use our Website, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Website or the domains from which Users originate. We may use “cookies” to track how Users use our Website. A cookie is a piece of software that a Web server can store on the UsersÃ¢â‚¬â„¢ PC and use to identify the User should they visit the Website again. While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our Website.
How We Use Information Knight Web Services® Inc. may use personally identifiable information collected through our Website to contact Users regarding products and services offered by Knight Web Services® Inc. and its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners, and otherwise to enhance Users’ experience with Knight Web Services® Inc. and such affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. Knight Web Services® Inc. may also use information collected through our Website for research regarding the effectiveness of the Website and the marketing, advertising and sales efforts of Knight Web Services® Inc., its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. At no time will Knight Web Services® Inc.’s database of users ever be sold to any entity for the purpose of marketing or mailing lists.
Disclosure of Information Knight Web Services® Inc. may disclose information collected from Users to trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners who will use the information for the purposes outlined above. We may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from Users to investors and potential partners. Finally, we may transfer information collected from Users in connection with a sale of Knight Web Services® Inc.’s business.
Maintenance of Information Information about Users that is maintained on our systems is protected using industry standard security measures. However, we cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on, or transmitted from our systems will be completely secure.
Questions Users may direct questions concerning this statement by e-mail to: webmaster@knightwebservices.com. Users may elect not to receive solicitations from Knight Web Services® Inc. or from trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners by letting us know or use the unsubscribe link contained in every message.
[printfriendly]
Content Management System (CMS)
Knight Web Services® Inc.
539 W. Commerce St. Ste. 1524
Dallas, TX 75208
Phone:
1-800-733-0368
Mail:
sales@knightwebservices.com
Copyright ©1996-2020 Knight Web Services® Inc. - All rights reserved.
